

MIHRIBAN ŞEYDA TATAR

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Prishtina +383 49 345 506

m.seydatatar@gmail.com Şeyda Tatar

Portfolio Website

PROFILE

Highly motivated, diligent software engineer with 1 year experience in full stack programming at a company operating in the global market. Proficient in software development life-cycle from design, development and testing of user interfaces to managing databases. Committed to teamwork and innovation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

FMT Group

June 2021 - August 2022

in

- Developed six modules corresponding to company departments for a CRM software in the form of a responsive web application using HTML, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, jQuery.
- Designed, created and maintained MySQL database.
- Maintained, repaired and updated existing CRM modules while regularly interacting with the users and adding functionalities to increase work efficiency.
- Gained experience in designing and developing Admin Dashboards.
- Conducted regular meetings with top company managers and other departments in order to
 understand the gaps and problems in the supply chain management. Implemented these business
 needs and functional requirements in the CRM software to help the whole chain for daily
 operation and Directors' reports.
- Worked closely with a Senior Programmer as well as the Research & Development Department.

MENTOR

Women In Tech Project

March 2020 - June 2020

- Spoke at the opening ceremony
- Mentored students aged 15-19 for a month of training to learn programming basics and coding in Java.

SKILLS

- JavaScript / TypeScript
- React
- Sass / Styled Components
- HTML / CSS / Bootstrap

- NoSQL / MySQL
- PHP
- Node.js
- Java

EDUCATION

 Java - Angular Internship / Training iKons

2022 February - July

Bachelor in International Relations
 Anadolu University

2020 - 2024

Bachelor in Software Engineering
 Canadian Institute of Technology
 GPA: 3.99

2018 - 2021

LANGUAGES

Turkish - Native

Albanian - Proficient

English - Fluent

Korean - Intermediate

INTERESTS

- Reading
- Art

- Languages
- Traveling